[Setup]
Title = Data Collection 

[Intro]
We ask you to help improve our application and/or products by providing usage information. 

[Desc]
Regarding data collection, please read the PRIVACY POLICY as follows.

[Main]
PRIVACY POLICY
<br>
<br>
This application uses Google Analytics, an analytical service provided by Google Inc., to gather and help analyze information on how users use this application and/or network printers. This information helps us improve the quality of this application and/or the products.
<br>
<br>The application does not collect any personal data.
<br>
<br> For details, please see www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/

