[Setup]
Title = Resource and Energy Saving

[Resource Saving]
Resource Saving - Paper
<br>
For the preservation and sustainable use of forest resources, it is 
recommended that recycled as well as virgin paper certified under 
environmental stewardship initiatives or carrying  recognized 
ecolabels, which meet EN 12281:2002*1 or an equivalent quality 
standard, be used.
<br>
This machine also supports printing on 64 g/m^2 paper.  Using such 
paper containing less raw materials can lead to further saving of 
forest resources.
<br>
*1: EN12281:2002 “Printing and business paper - Requirements for 
copy paper for dry toner imaging processes”
<br>

[Energy Efficiency]
Energy Efficiency - Energy Star (ENERGY STAR®) Program
<br>
ENERGY STAR® is a voluntary energy efficiency program with the goal 
of developing and promoting the use of products with high energy 
efficiency in order to help prevent global warming. By purchasing 
ENERGY STAR® qualified products, customers can help reduce emissions 
of greenhouse gases during product use and cut energy-related costs.
<br>

[Duplex Printing]
Environmental benefits of “Duplex Printing”
<br>
Printing in duplex mode reduces paper consumption and contributes 
to the conservation of forest resources.  Duplex mode also reduces 
the amount of paper that must be purchased, and thereby reduces cost. 
It is recommended that machines capable of duplex printing be set to 
use duplex mode by default.
<br>

[Power Management]
Environmental benefits of “Power Management”
<br>
To reduce power consumption when idle, this machine is equipped 
with a power management function that automatically activates energy-saving 
mode when the machine is idle for a certain period of time. Although it 
takes the machine a slight amount of time to return to READY mode when in 
energy-saving mode, a significant reduction in energy consumption is 
possible. It is recommended that the machine be used with the activation 
time for energy-saving mode set to the default setting.
